Johnnie Hicks

Full Stack Developer

EMAIL

johnnie432@icloud.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/johnnie-hicks-a3990320a/

GITHUB

https://github.com/Johnnie007

PORTFOLIO

http://www.johnnieh.me

PHONE

PHONE: +1-321-505-4198

I possess a can-do attitude to any situation or obstacle. Also, I have gained valuable knowledge and experience through school and my past jobs. My education has taught me how to make great practical choices and manage my time wisely. In my work experience, I gained some soft skills such as social intelligence, work ethic, resilience, and team management.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Document Object Model (DOM) APIs, Node.js, Express.js, Web APIs, User Authentication, OAuth,: Heroku, GitHub, WebPack, MySQL

EXPERIENCE

Sonder

Guest Experience Agent MAY 2019 - MAR 2020, Denver, CO

Summary: Sonder is a tech startup in the hospitality industry. I gained valuable Soft skills such as communication, teamwork, leadership, decision making, conflict resolution, creativity, and empathy.

- Responded to, troubleshooted, and resolved guest issues in a timely manner.
- The first point of contact for all our guests via phone, email and chat
- Coordinated with the city teams to resolve issues on the ground and provide ongoing updates to guests.

Aerotek

Temporary Associate

JAN 2016 - JAN 2019, Jacksonville, FL

Summary: Aerotek is a staffing firm where I worked as a contractor for two companies (Steinmart and Gusto). The skills that I gained were: Networking, Self Motivation, teamwork, responsibility, decisiveness, and flexibility.

- Assisted contract employers with goal based projects.
- Reviewed projects and fixed errors before submitting to the Project Manager.

DriveTime

Operation Advisor

AUG 2015 - May 2016, Jacksonville, FL

Summary: Drivetime is a car dealership where I worked closely with the general manager with reports and contracts. Soft skills gained were: critical observation, work ethic, time management, listening, and writing skills.

- Managed financials for vehicles and served as liaison for outsourced vendors.
- Analyzed contracts to ensure adherence to corporate standards.
- Reconciled and managed the budget for the dealership.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma Candidate, Web Development

APR 2021 - JUN 2021, Miami, FI

12-Week Immersive Bootcamp. I learned how to write and update software throughout the course. I created new applications from start to finish, as well as updated already existing code. Also, I engineered new features for my existing applications.

Jacksonville University | Bachelors in Business Administration

AUG 2011 - AUG 2015, Jacksonville, FL

A four year degree in Business Administration, throughout my major I gained valuable leadership skills, how to make great practical choices, and time management skills.